question_data = [{"question": "Adolf Hitler was tried at the Nuremberg trials.",
                  "correct_answer": "False"},
                 {"question": "The Spitfire originated from a racing plane.",
                  "correct_answer": "True"},
                 {
                     "question": "The United States was a member of the League of Nations.",
                     "correct_answer": "False"},
                 {
                     "question": "The United States of America declared their independence from the British Empire on July 4th, 1776.",
                     "correct_answer": "True"},
                 {
                     "question": "The United States of America was the first country to launch a man into space.",
                     "correct_answer": "False"},
                 {
                     "question": "In World War ll, Great Britian used inflatable tanks on the ports of Great Britain to divert Hitler away from Normandy\/D-day landing.",
                     "correct_answer": "True"},
                 {
                     "question": "Former United States Presidents John Adams and Thomas Jefferson died within hours of each other.",
                     "correct_answer": "True"},
                 {
                     "question": "The French Kingdom helped the United States gain their independence over Great Britain during the Revolutionary War.",
                     "correct_answer": "True"},
                 {
                     "question": "The Cold War ended with Joseph Stalin&#039;s death.",
                     "correct_answer": "False"},
                 {
                     "question": "Kublai Khan is the grandchild of Genghis Khan?",
                     "correct_answer": "True"}]
